Okay. So, today I have someone very very
interesting here. Monday to Friday I
would go to uni 8 to 6 and Saturday
Sunday it's not even a 9 to 5. It was 11
to 11. Oh wow. 12 hour shift. Yeah. And
from that moment onwards my only focus
was make €800 a month online for myself.
I like I said I'm no name. I have
nothing to my name. I can't really sell
expensive stuff to brands or close big
deals on my name cuz I have nothing to
my name. Now if I go and I pull an
influencer Mhm. and then use his social
proof and sell this. I don't have to
build a brand. I don't have to do it for
I just have to do the sales. And I never
heard anyone come to me and talk about
someone's project delivering results for
their students. And the way they spoke
about you, man, it works. Like
literally, it works. We have a student
that closed
48,000 US worth of deals in his second
month. Oh wow. The moment you're the
closest to Allahel is in sujud, you
basically have 34 opportunities every
single day to ask the one who built
everything to help you with any sort of
problem you have. Anytime you're trying
to achieve something new, trying to
start a business, trying to get married,
trying to get in a trying to make hij
anything you want to achieve, you'd be
saying it became it became a habit and
then you realize after saying it, wait,
it's been granted already. Sorry guys,
I'm in public right now. I hate doing
these videos in public cuz you don't
know who's around. But I was genuinely
shocked by this. You see me, I don't
actually work with anyone that's not
doing at least six figures annually
because it's so hard to take someone
from zero to one. And that is why I
respect brother Abu, the brother I
interviewed in this podcast so much
because he's dedicated his mission to
doing exactly just that, helping
beginners make their first bit of money
online. And his coaching program is not
just hype because, wait for it, he's got
a 100% success rate. That's unheard of.
100% of those who coaches that go
through his entire program start making
money within three months and he's
helped several students doing well over
$10,000 a month. Allah he's basically
the Muslim version of Alex Ramosi who's
known to just take these complicated
sophisticated business concepts and make
them so simple and easily actionable
that even an absolute novice when it
comes to business can just follow it
step by step and then start making money
with Allah's permission. And that is
what brother Abu La does. Now, for those
of you who want to know more about how
to do this and how he and his students
are doing this, this podcast is an
absolute watch for you. And for those of
you who consider yourself maybe a bit
more serious and want to dive into
entrepreneurship and have him as a
coach, I've linked his program directly
below. But just a heads up, it's
actually a very hard program to get
into. They've got very, very high
qualification standards. They've had
well over 10,000 applications, the
overwhelming majority of which they've
rejected.
And it's also not cheap. It's also not
cheap. But with the type of resource
he's getting students, it's worth every
penny. So you can check him out the link
below. With that said, I love and
respect this brother so much. Let's get
into our podcast.
Alhamdulillah. Okay. So today I have
someone very very interesting here.
Brother Abah, how you doing?
Alhamdulillah. Good.
I'm really honored to have you here
sitting in front of me and uh we've been
speaking and in all transparency you
know mashallah you're a phenomenal
entrepreneur Allah and Barik I've had
calls with you where you know you've
given advice to me and given me insight
helped me tweak our offers and
alhamdulillah
uh we have some mutual friends that are
now working with you as well and they
mentioned so many great things about you
to me you know brother Zade brother Aman
they were like bro this brother
his mentorship it works like literally
it works Allahbar and I never heard
anyone come to me and talk about
someone's project delivering results for
their students and the way they spoke
about you manic relax my ears going to
start getting big my going to get big
chill appreciate it so look talk to me
man every everyone has a start when it
comes to this entrepreneurial
journey where did yours begin like what
was the thing that drove you to say I'm
going to do my own business.
So, I'd
say I always wanted to make money. Okay.
And then it was just a question of how.
So, I when I was younger, I thought, you
know, just get a job, just get a better
job. That's how you make a lot of money.
You're either a doctor, a lawyer, you
know, something like that. Mhm.
Then I started realizing there are other
opportunities which are people working
for themselves having their own
businesses and making money. To me it
was wild. You could either get paid by
someone a lot of money or inherit uh you
know a large amount and that's how you
make that was your only two options.
Yeah. To me you either get it and give
it to you or you know you got a nice
degree and then you continue getting
paid. You couldn't like build your own
company build everything from scratch
and and make it. To me that was like
something they talk about in the movies
not not in reality.
And then alhamdulillah I started seeing
a couple of guys on YouTube. Crazy
seeing that now I was speaking about
guys I was seeing on YouTube and now we
we are posting stuff on YouTube. Um but
I was seeing some some people talk about
it was back in 2016
when you know they started with drop
shipping they started posting about
ecom. Um that was that was the main
niche that also was SMMA with with
Imangazi that came in a bit later and
that gave me insights on you can make
money with different ways not just
having a job or inheriting your money.
Um and then slowly that drive to make
money shifted to a drive to start a
business. Mhm. And the main driver
actually I speak a lot about money but
it was more about independence and
capability. So it was being see how with
both path that I had you either inherit
so you depend on whoever gave you money
or you got paid with a great job so it
depend on the company that pays you. You
were always dependent and reliant on the
other entity that pay you. Mhm.
Well the third way I found which is
starting your business is where you are
the one who builds everything. You're
the one who who brings the wealth and
you have no cap on how much you can
benefit from it. You can have your own
decisions. You can rely on yourself.
You're not dependent. And that is the
main
thing. That's that's the main thing I
was I was looking for. The freedom.
That's the the freedom. So you mentioned
there was a turning point. You had a
job. You used to work for someone and
you had an experience that led you to
think, you know what, I can't work for
this guy anymore. I have to Nothing
against the brother. Muslim guy, lovely
guy. Allah bless him. Till this day,
love him. And the turning point was
super good for me. Mhm. But so what was
the story? It was Ramadan. Yeah. So it
goes back to when I was working uh it's
not even a 9 to5. It was 11 to 11. Oh
wow. 12 hour shift. Yeah. Crazy. Um and
I was working on weekends cuz I was
going uni in the I was working on
weekends cuz I was going uni in the
during the week. Okay. So Saturday,
Sundays I would work 11 to 11. Okay. Um
so sorry, Monday to Friday I would go to
uni 8 to 6. Uhhuh. And Saturday, Sunday,
I go to the restaurant. 11 to 11. Yeah.
Now came Ramadan. I I was serving uh
Pokeball. So I was serving rice and and
and uh and salmon. Japanese food. Yeah.
Japanese concept. Um then came that's
what I was doing throughout the year.
Then came Ramadan and I realized I
didn't know at the time that you can't
sell food cuz I was living in France.
You can't sell food during the day.
People don't fast and you can't have a
restaurant. A lot of people don't know
this, right? But Allah says in the
Quran do not encourage each other in sin
and transgression. So people who are in
even if they're not Muslims, they should
be Muslim and they should be fasting in
the month of Ramadan. So for that reason
the scholars they mentioned you can't
serve them food even if they're not
Muslim because at that time they should
be fasting. Yeah. Right. They should be
fasting. So you're encouraging them in
transgression. you took that view and
you said look I cannot serve food. Yeah.
I came to the to the brother I was like
I and I did I needed the money at the
time but still um that's a point we can
touch on later. You know when you give
up something for you always get better.
Um but yeah I I I told him I can't I
can't serve food. Do you have anything
else I could do? I really you know I'm
I'm up. I don't mind carrying heavy
stuff. Just it's it's something decent.
I make money. I'm good. Mhm. Um he was
like let me you know he had like a
studio he had to renovate repaint a wall
had to carry some stuff clean like I was
cool. Mhm. So alhamdulillah I took um
the job for that month everything goes
well first few weeks I was still working
uh just weekends. First weekend goes
well. Second weekend and then a third
weekend he he had like a a storage room.
Okay. In one of his restaurants called
he he was a serious entrepreneur. So he
had like couple restaurants and
everything.
And he was Muslim. So that also one of
the things that opened my eyes to like
having a business. Uhhuh.
Um he had one of these other
restaurants, a pizza shop. And No, he he
had Yeah. He had one of his other
restaurants. It was a I think a pizza
shop. Okay. or um or snack. He he was
selling some some some food. I forgot
what the crepes. Do you know crepes?
Creps. Yeah. Yeah. Crap. Yeah. Yeah. So
he had a he had another restaurant. He
was selling creps and in the storage
room of that restaurant he had like a
fridge. Mhm. They unplugged the fridge
for 3 months cuz the thing, you know, it
didn't didn't really work. So they
stopped running the restaurant. They
left it like it was. And then my job was
to clean the mess. M. It was fine until
I had to go to that fridge where I open
it up. Madness. Disgusting. Yeah.
Really? Like Amazon forest. Amazon
forest. Mushrooms. Like wild. Because
they left everything like tomatoes. How
big fridge? That was like family size
fridge. Okay. And like restaurant size.
I mean they stoing the entire they would
store the entire inventory. Oh wow. So
this is massive. Yeah. And but that's
that was not the the crazy part. I'm
like cool. I take gloves. I take plastic
bags and I just start throwing
everything like was fine. But then they
had you see the middle box where they
hold the like the you know when you go
to um a restaurant and they they serve
you like they make salad in front of
you. They have those metal box where
they like they had that with like
tomatoes inside cheese and they also
left those. So like it's big metal box
that you you keep reusing. You don't
throw them. But it was food was so
rotten and like was sticking to the the
middle box. I was like, I'm going to
throw everything. It cost it cost like
€2. I was like, I'm going to buy them
again. I'm just going to throw them
throw those and buy new ones. Uh
probably the thing was was was so rusted
you couldn't use it anyway. Mhm.
And then he came up to check on on that
later that day. He came up to check on
the fridge. He was like, "Yeah, uh great
cleaning, but where are the boxes?" And
I was like, "Yeah, they're there. I'm
going to throw them with everything else
cuz it's rotten." And I was like, "No,
no, we're going to keep them. You're
going to wash them. We're going to keep
it." And then I was like, I don't want
to complain or like give headaches and
everything. I'm always happy to work.
But I was like, like I can't do that.
Like even the the the storage room, it
was you had kind of a how do you call
it? Yeah. Cuz even in the in the storage
room, you had just a small sink with
nothing. So I was just cleaning stuff
with water. You didn't even have soap.
You didn't have like a sponge to clean
up stuff like done with your hands. It
was It was mad.
And I had to like scrape the food with
like a fork. It was a big mess. And I
was like, I can't I can't like I went
far already. I didn't complain. Didn't
say nothing cuz I took the job. Then I
was like, there's no way I'm cleaning.
Like I can't do that. I'd rather buy
them again. No problem. Um even if he
takes my whole paycheck for the day, but
I'm not I can't I can't do
that. And then had a little argument.
And one thing he told me which he was in
the right. I really my point is not to
backfire the Muslim brother or anything.
He he was in the right but he told me
after argument like I said like yeah I
can't do that. And he was like yeah but
I'm paying you so you don't really have
a choice.
And when he said
that, like first of all, he fired me up.
First of all, like I'm Algerian. So Al,
I was just going to say he's that
Algerian. Anything you say can fire
someone quickly, but I mean, especially
as Algerian, they say our blood is, you
know, is hotter than than average.
Um, he was Algerian, too, so he could
have went crazy. But I was
like, and I was like, he's right. like
the the the little the big voice inside
me was like, "I'm gonna get, you know,
something's going to go crazy. How can
you say that to me?" And everything. The
the reasonable voice was like, "He's
right. He's saying the truth." And from
that moment, I was making like 800 a
month with that job. My only goal from
there was to make the same amount, but
just online or just with with my own
ways, not relying on someone because I
felt so weak when he said that. I was
like, "He's right. I can't like I'm
depending on him paying me for me to
make money. So if he decides somehow to
make me do something I don't want to
do. I don't really have a choice. If I
signed up for it or for something
similar and I'm relying on him, I got to
do what basically I don't have my
freedom or my my freedom of choice,
freedom of actions. Even though I'm
getting paid and I feel like money would
give me that freedom for the job I'm
doing, I don't have the freedom of
picking what I do. And from that moment
onwards, my only focus was make €800 a
month online for myself. This influencer
marketing agency thing, how did you land
on this particular idea? Because it's
like, for example, someone who strikes
oil in his back garden. Mhm. Who placed
the oil there? Yeah. Allah. Right. And I
think that's a very important point
because I noticed that you mention this
a lot. It's a theme in pretty much I
think every single one of your videos
which is to always make sure that your
business is halal rely upon Allah to
fear Allah subhana wa ta'ala.
Allah Allah subhanahu wa ta'ala said if
you fear Allah Allah will provide for
you from a place that you never
imagined. Like you probably never
imagined that you were going to one day
do an influence marking. I never
actually the story on how I landed on it
was crazy. How what was the story? So I
I I covered it once.
Um I was you see from that moment in the
restaurant when I was I had that you
know uh it was around Ramadan a couple
of years ago. Mhm. I from that moment
like I said I wanted I was like I need
to make money online. That's for sure. I
need to make my own money. I had no idea
where to start. First thing I did is I
bought a course. Now I was so broke.
Course was like €300. It's not even a
crazy course. I could not even afford
this course. Mhm. So, I went and he he
was running like a kind of a a discount
on on a special offer. I got it down to
€100. I was still so broke. I still
couldn't buy it, but didn't want to buy
at this price. So, I went with a friend
of mine and split the price. Oh, wow.
How how crazy how how far went. Some
people would just say, "I can't afford
it. It's done."
From there, it was not even related to
influencing. It was related to some
Twitter, make money online with Twitter,
um doing some post and everything.
I've I bought this course and then
inside there was a community. Mhm.
I landed on some Muslim brothers. He was
a French guy. No, it was not towards
Muslim at all. But inside the groups
always, you know, Muslims, they
recognize each other and then we just
got together. We made a smaller group
within that group of Muslims. And some
of these brothers found an alternative
to what he was doing. Uhhuh. That was
basically the guy would teach you how to
make money on Twitter by selling
courses. They went in the other route of
making money on Twitter by getting
sponsorships.
So I just basically was like this makes
sense. I see people getting sponsored I
think and and they were building their
own Twitter accounts to get sponsorships
on their own accounts. Okay. Now I
started doing this and it started taking
a lot of time. I was like it's taking 2
months. I don't get followers. I'm
posting every day. It doesn't work. And
then one day I realized I was like,
"Wait, I know many guys from that group
that have an account that's making
money, but they're not at full capacity
yet. They can still take on more
workload." I was like, "Imagine if I
just fill out this this capacity that
was going to be nothing. They wouldn't
have any sponsorship." Like, let's say
they can do five sponsorship a week. Get
the sponsorships. Yeah. Oh, wow. A lot
better. And then I was like, then I
don't need a brand. I don't need social
media. Of course, I'll make way less
money. Let's say I just make 20% of the
the of the of the deal, but I do it for
five different people. And you don't
have to do any fulfillment.
I don't have to build the brand. I don't
have to do the fulfillment. I just have
to do the sales.
Then you did that. I did that. So, and
that's my point, right? Like, you know,
there's two names of allahel that I
think every single entrepreneur has to
live by. And I'm going to go into these
in a bit more detail during the retreat,
inshallah.
And um the reason I say entrepreneur
because there's a dua the prophet taught
us to make every night before we sleep
where we
say oh Allah pay off our debts help us
pay off our debts and enrich us make us
rich from pro but allahel mentions some
of his names before that and there's two
that I want to mention very specifically
so it's in the context of
Allah, you are the first. There's
nothing before you. And Allah, you're
the last and there's nothing after you.
And there's a huge amount of knowledge
connected to what this means. But I want
to talk about it from a spiritual angle.
And that is that before your business,
forget business, before you existed,
Allah was there. You never wanted to
exist. You
never had an idea or a want or a desire
to exist. But Allah brought you to into
existence out of his virtue and his
father right out of his he just said I'm
going to
bring I'm going to bring them into
existence and then you will die and I
will die. But he's he's the one who
always
remains. So he will keep
you he will allow you to remain in
paradise with his permission. So he is
the one who brings you into existence
before you even wanted to and he is the
one who will allow you to remain even
after your expiry date because of his
mercy and his father and his virtue.
Likewise in terms of your business,
allahel like what we don't realize is
before the idea even came before you
even knew you were going to do it. Like
Allah was there first and he decreed and
guided you to this particular
transaction and then after he guid you
to that transaction influencer marketing
agency he is the one who will allow that
business to remain and carry on growing
and growing as long as you connect
yourself to the one who remains and not
the business cuz the business will
always go and die out and so on and so
forth. I think there's a huge element of
that
um in terms of your dealing perhaps with
business and your dealings with allahel
that I think that's allowed you to see
that success and hopefully inshallah
also also your
students and you talk about it a lot
which is why I feel like it would be a
travesty to not touch upon this because
like I've seen guys man that do
everything right when it comes to
business and still they don't make the
money right like one plus one plus one
you know businesses That one thing
that it shows you is from Allah cuz you
can literally do every single logical
step and still not make money. Mhm.
Right. There is that secret ingredient
of Allah. There's another one that what
you're saying is beautiful. But there's
also the other side which is you can not
be doing every single thing right but
you're right with your relationship with
allahel. You have baraka and that
patches the holes
and that is the one that people Muslims
don't understand. We have like an unfair
advantage. I I genuinely believe we have
like a cheat code. People saying like oh
we can't do I'm like we literally have
cheat codes. So someone who built the
game tells you look I built games.
Here's how to win. Here's how to lose.
I'm giving you the the rules. I'm also
giving you literally the ways to not
fail. And somehow he's saying, "Wait,
I'm so unlucky to have the ways of
winning the game." How how crazy does
that sound like? Very crazy. Subhan
Allah. And also he gives you cheat
codes. He tells you, "Look,
you want to invest, you have all the
ways to invest your money. You can
invest your money. You have, you know,
you can buy companies, you can buy, you
can invest your money, you can buy real
estate, etc. Or you can give charity."
Mhm. And I will multiply your wealth.
Mhm. Imagine you're a Cafe. You're
missing out on that. Yeah. like your
only options are like there's actually
studies right now there's an econ
economist that came out I did a video on
it on my
channel people who give charity
statistically make one and a half times
more money than people who don't give
charity and wall the guy was asked why
do you think that is he said I don't
know it seems like an act of god right
and then he he's a non-Muslim and then
he tried to philosophize it and say you
know I guess it's because guys who give
charity are people that think more about
you know uh how to better society so
they have that mindset and you know but
he said it at the beginning like I done
I done two videos of it on my channel
one on my Instagram one on my YouTube
it's mind-blowing and then there's a
prophet the prophet said every single
morning there are two angels who call
out and they make a dua one says just a
quick question did you know that the
majority of millionaires are made
through real estate now this was crazy
to me when I found out because obviously
as a businessman as an entrepreneur
who's trying to make as much money as
possible you'd focus on the thing that's
driving people the most amount of
results. And there's decades and
centuries of proof that real estate
helps create millionaires. But then
there's one fundamental issue which is
that as a Muslim who's trying to fear
Allahel not engage in ribba and
interest. It's very hard to engage in
real estate because if you don't have
that upfront capital to invest, you take
a loan, but there's going to be ribba
interest and then no one wants to start
a war with Allahhanaa. Which is why I
believe it's such a blessing that we
have people like brother Sam in our umah
today who actually took the initiative
to create models and infrastructure to
help Muslims invest and make millions
through real estate without even a
single debt without a penny of ribba.
Brother Sam has over $und00 million of
Muslim money invested in real estate
100% ribba free. is investors are
fortune 100 senior executives and some
of the investors that have invested in
his projects have become millionaires on
the back of the investments they've done
with him and I have personally met some
of them with the permission of allahel
currently there are projects in Medina
the city of the prophet sallallahu
alaihi was sallallahu alaihi wasallam
which is 100% over subscribed projects
in the US and there are some very
exciting projects here in Dubai the
investors are seeing doubledigit returns
in as short as just one year this is a
crazy and ridiculous opportunity. Now,
initially, you had to have $100,000
minimum to invest in these real estate
projects with a mean developments, but
now, alhamdulillah, an infrastructure
has been set up and created for you guys
to be able to enter with as little as
$50,000. That's right, $50,000 100% put
towards a ribbree project with
double-digit returns within one year.
This is a crazy and ridiculous
opportunity. So, if you guys want to
find more information about how you can
get involved and more details on the
project and see if you qualify and
eligible to be part of his investors,
click on the link below, fill in the
form, and get on a call to one of his
team members. With that said, let's get
back to the
podcast. Oh, the one who is giving, give
him more. Oh Allah, the one who is
withholding, give him destruction. So
it's funny cuz you we think we need to
make money in order to give charity but
the prophet is teaching us you need to
give charity in order to make money.
Yeah. So you're right that's a cheat
code. And talking about the charity part
you have three
different levels when it comes to giving
charity. Mhm. So let's say you have
£1,000 to your name. You have three
zones when it comes to to giving
charity. You have the green zone, the
comfort zone which is you're giving £10,
20. And that's that's easy. That's
decision you make like this. Someone
comes and asks you like, "Yeah, he's
just going to leave me alone if I give
him£10." Easy. And forget about it. Then
you have the yellow zone where you start
to get a bit more serious. You think
more when you're going going to the give
this charity. You start to get a bit
scared, but you're like, I I'll trust
Allah. And you still know that worst
case, you're not going too deep. Let's
say you're giving £100, for example.
We're giving £200. It's a lot for you.
20% of what you have, but you know,
worst case, you can survive. You have
backup plans. Mhm.
Now those two are are good. The last one
is great. The last one is the red one.
The last one is the danger zone. Is
where you you you see when you have it
ever happened to you that you gave
charity and you felt like oh I went too
far. Did I exceed? Did I did I wait? I
didn't I didn't think I had this bill.
Wait, how we going to make rent? But you
knew when you gave that charity at the
moment before giving it, it was the
right thing to do. But then after you
start to panic and realize you went too
far, that is the exact amount you should
have to give. Mhm. Because that is the
tangible proof of you relying on Allahel
for everything. You
have you have you know you have the
proof of I can say I have I can say I I
I trust Allah. Let's say there's a guy
that says I trust Allah. I make dua
every day. I pray my five salawat. I
make sure everything I do is halal
because I trust Allah and I trust him to
give me everything. And now this is Mr.
A. Now we have Mr.
who does the same thing but also he
gives abundantly and he does not look
when he gives. Mhm. And he goes in and
puts himself in sometimes tough spots.
Mhm. But still it's for the sake of
Allah. Which one can come in and say I
have real or I have the best because
they could they both have real. I'm not
saying one is is bad the other one is
good. I'm saying which one has the most
someone has tangible proof they can
touch. It's interesting because the
hadith actually
mentions charity is a proof proof of
your iman your im your dean you know
your connection to allahel no 100% agree
with
you the that is definitely a cheat code
another cheat code that you talk about
is uh just before we leave that one take
an action right now if you're watching
this video and you have not much to your
name give most of what you have I'm I'm
genuinely telling you this is one of the
best things you could have let's say you
have 200 to your name M how about you go
and you give all of that away? Like
worst case what's going to happen on
your life? You're not we're not going to
go super far anyway with £200. Of
course, if you have a family, rent to
pay, stay within don't put your family
in trouble. That's what not what I'm
saying. But there's a a real wisdom in
charity. We could probably do a whole
podcast on charity on on all the
benefits you can have. Sometimes you
have problems you have no idea how to
solve them. Sometimes I have a simple
code. That's why being Muslims is
so good. Even for just for pure
businesswise, if someone was a pure
hypocrite and just looked for himself, I
think he should be he should
still I think he would if he has logic,
he would become a Muslim just for all
the advantages you have. Not even for
the the spiritual and and and everything
else just because of all the advantages
you have. You know, like on the charity
thing, just to kind of break down people
like you know how simple it is, you
know, the prophet sallallahu alaihi
wasallam said that the best charity you
can give is water. Like if you just go
to one of those convenience stores, buy
like a six-pack and just go and just
give to the people. They don't even have
to be poor people. People don't realize
it doesn't even have to be poor people.
Just be giving water to people smiling,
you know, here you go, here you go, here
you go. But I
said, and I actually know a brother who
was going through a very, very, very,
very tough time
financially, very tough time.
nothing, zero coming in, right? And I
think he had maybe just like a, you
know, very small amount of dirham. He
went and basically he got some packs of
water and you know the delivery drivers
and the Talibat drivers here, you know,
they're the motorbikes very hot. They're
driving, you know, all day every day.
Just started handing them out and he
said, "Ya Allah, I'm doing this." And
this is all I have. I think it cost
maybe like the equivalent of €3 to buy
these packs of water. He just gave them
out and said, "Ya Allah, this is all I
have, but I'm doing this for your sake."
And then, subhan Allah, the brother's
situation, wall, he completely turned
around. He just every day he would just
do that. He would just go to the masjid,
he would buy some packs, give it, and
then he said, "Literally, I saw
literally days after that, my financial
situation completely turned around." And
the lesson with that we conclude on that
point with this
is you see as as men you always the one
who's responsible you always look have
to look out for your family have to look
out for your wife have to be the one
provides you always has the
responsibility your wife can can say oh
yeah I'm not I'm not caring anything
about the bills you're handling
everything and that's your job
and alhamdulillah that's that's what
we've been you know uh created for I
mean you know besides worshiping allahel
that's why as men that's our roles
That's what I meant. Um,
but sometimes like, yeah, we never have
the chance to just give it up and be
like, "Let me relax or let me not figure
everything. I have to." It's part of our
job except once. Mhm. When you won't
allow to fix things for you. And I do
this all the time. I don't understand
why people try and figure everything out
themselves. I'm like, there's someone
who I mean, allahel built the game and
I'm playing the game and you're telling
me I can ask him to help me win in the
game and you're going to try and figure
out everything yourself. Like, you're
going to try and play solo when people
are playing like team mode. Like, how
does that make sense? How arrogant is
that? Especially when when the team mode
is literally you and Allah. Like, how
crazy does it sound? You're right. It
sounds pretty crazy. So, let's say you
have nothing to your name. you can't
figure everything out. Even it happens
at any stage, by the way. It could be
when you're completely trying to go from
0 to 1, 1 to 10, 10 to 100. Anytime when
you have a bottleneck, you don't know
how to solve it, turn your brain off, go
please, he'll sort you out. Like all the
times your business is not working, just
look, okay, what can I do good for
people? How can I help other people so
that Allahel helps me? It's sometimes
much much easier. How easy would it be
for you right now to help someone? Let's
say you're level 10. Mhm. How easy would
it be for you to have someone go to from
level two to five? Like pretty easy.
You've done it a lot of times. Yeah, of
course. Yeah. Then go and do this and
help him get from two to five and then
Allahel who's who built all the levels,
he can help you get 10 to 100 just like
you have the other guy and see how easy
it was for you. Imagine for the one who
built the entire game.
Before we conclude, there's another
cheat code you talk about, right? Which
is the
sujud cheat code. So talk to us about
this one cuz I think most of the people
a lot of people who signed up to your
program actually mentioned that this was
one thing that Yeah. Somehow people
Yeah. It stood out to people. I don't
know why I said it on the go in in in
one video and um and it stood out to
people. So you see how we have five
daily prayers and if you count all the
ra that we have we have 17
from now each has two
sujuds that means okay so let's save
that each has two sujuds we have 34
sujud a day okay we're putting this on a
note now another thing Allah
said the closest you are to him is when
you're in sujud right if you can even
quote the the verse you you're the
closer he He's closer to you. That's
another thing I think. Okay. Um the
closest is is
injud and get close to me. Allah says he
commands us make sud and get closer to
him and and especially making dua in
your sujud. So now you know that the
moment you're the closest to allahel is
in sujud and that you have 34 sujud a
day you basically have 34 opportunities
every single day to ask the one who
built everything to help you with any
sort of problem you have.
And my advice for for people is actually
a tip and I genuinely hope people take
it from this from this podcast and and
spread it cuz that would be the the best
you can do. Anytime you're trying to
achieve something new, trying to start a
business, trying to get married, trying
to get in a trying to make anything you
want to achieve. It could be even as
small as just succeeding with your
exams. Mhm.
Make a specific dua. Let's say it could
be as simple as, "Oh, help me succeed
with my exams." my math exams. It could
be this, you know, you're really bad at
math and you're like, "Oh, please help
me get, you know, 60% on at math. I'm
really bad." Just this and make it in
every single sujud that you in every
single prayer in every single sujud.
Just this. Repeat it. Repeat it.
Continue doing it until it becomes a
habit. And you'll catch yourself after a
couple of weeks, couple of months
depending on when Allahel decides to
accept your dua. You'll be saying it as
a habit. Sometimes just a couple of days
after that you'd be saying it become it
became a habit and then you realize
after saying it wait it's been granted
already and you go
from saying and asking to and then you
go from asking Allah to give you that
thing from to thanking him for giving
you this and you you catch yourself even
like I said it could be with everything
let's say I've seen that myself you
spoke about it I've seen that myself
that happened to me right and you're
like well subhan Allah wait I should be
thanking him now cuz he gave it to me.
Mhm. And and I can even look back at my
life and have checkpoints on my
achievements. And I had each time a
specific focus on on one specific day I
was making. Whether it could be the
school I wanted to get, whether it could
be the job I wanted to get, whether it
would be the business I wanted to start.
Always there was a specific time where I
was focusing on making this dua to
Allah. And then I always caught myself.
It was a habit. And then boom, it was
granted. went from please can I get XY
and Z to thank you alhamdulillah for
giving me
XYZ man. So there are so many different
opportunities
online. You decided to set
up an affiliate marketing
an influencer marketing agency.
What led you to that as opposed to ecom,
digital marketing,
SMMA, Amazon FBA, all these other
things? So, there's something I'm going
to say and if you're watching this
video, please take that advice from me.
Don't don't buy any courses. Don't don't
do anything. I saw a course myself. I'm
telling
you before even thinking about business
models and what you want to do, look at
where you are. I have a couple of videos
covering that point. They're going to be
live soon. I really made it broken down
step by step. um that the the basic
thing you need to understand if you want
to make money online and you're a
beginner, you don't have experience, you
don't have
skills, most people want to make what 5
to 10k a month. Mhm. Like that's most
people would be good with that as a
starting point. Mhm. There's no other
reason for anyone to start any other
type of business besides a service based
business if you're trying to make 5 to
10k a month as a beginner, especially
online. As a beginner, if you're trying
to make 5 10k a month, you think you're
saying that you should basically only be
doing a service based business. Yes.
There's it would not make any sense to
do like you have product based. Let's
let's list the different types of of
businesses. You have product based
businesses. Okay. You have service based
businesses. Then you have online or
offline of course, but that's that's the
two main uh different categories. You
have software and everything. It's it's
kind of just services.
So with product based businesses by by
default any business that that has
physical products attached to it has so
much more overhead than a service based
business right there's capital you need
initially there's the capital the
product itself storage shipping it
that's just getting the product right
there just even when you made money
there's still headaches so like you sold
you you let's say you're doing ecom the
ecom guys are going to start hitting me
uh you have your store everything is is
is perfect first of all it was a whole
headache selling everything up getting
the right product. But let's say you've
done it. Now you sold products. After
that, you still have headaches. You
still have refunds, chargebacks, you
still have guys sitting by the product.
You still have interesting cuz you
mentioned in one of your videos you
said, and by the way, I'm not against
ecom or anything like that. But what I
do like about what you do is there are
some brothers that ecom just going to be
too sophisticated for them, right? But I
like that you allow people to access
entrepreneurship through this particular
business model who might not have the
knowhow of all the sophistications that
come with ecom. There was one thing that
you said that kind of really resonated
with me. You said in order to run an
ecom business, it's like you need to
master multiple different businesses at
the exact same time. So what do you mean
by that? I understood it, but just break
it down. The way it works that there are
different layers if you want to make
money online, offline is the same thing.
But let's just talk about money online
right now cuz that's what most people
try and do if they're watching the
podcast.
Um, when you're starting out, you have
no skills, no connections, nothing. The
only thing you have is time. So that's
the only thing you can sell. Mhm. So
when you're starting out, you're just
selling your time. That's where you are
a freelancer or like me, I was selling
my time in a restaurant, just getting a
job just to get paid. It's like to get
your head above water to survive. Mhm.
Then if you want to get to the next step
where you can have a better job, when
you can get paid more for your time, but
you got to add some skills to yourself.
You can't have more time. You still
enough of your time. you're already
working 10 hours a day. If you want to
make more, the only way for you to do it
is to make your time worth more money.
And to do this, you acquire skills that
allow you to help people in a in a
better way, have provide more value.
Basically, I don't want to start making
it sounds too complex. It's it's pretty
straightforward. You go from selling
your time to selling your time, but your
time is worth more. That's level two.
So, you got skills that allowed you for
your time to to be worth more. And even
we can put some some numbers on it. If
you, let's say, selling your time,
usually you get from zero to 2 grand a
month is fair. After that, you got to
start making your time worth more. So,
you can go from anywhere from two to 5
grand to be honest. So, when you're
selling your time, it's so things that
don't really require a skill, right?
Something that anyone can do. Clean the
floor. Yeah. Basically, VA, like basic
basic stuff, basic stuff. But then now
you're selling your skill with your time
that makes you more valuable. Okay.
Beautiful. Then after that you can
directly switch to you already have a
lot of skills you already have a lot
selling a lot of your time still you
capped so you have to start selling
other people's skills and other people's
time that's you start building a team
yeah you delegate you hire people you
train them they do service delivery for
you do client acquisition for you
basically is is how you scale and up
there until you want to make you know
eight figures a year that one is is
enough. Yeah. Now, the last one is when
you want to build an empire is when
you're going to go max level. And that's
where you're going to start selling your
expertise and your experience. Mh. And
you don't like you're already selling
your time cuz you're working. You
already have a lot of skills cuz you
have built, you know, many businesses
before. You already have a team that's
working with you and everything. And on
top of that, you're selling all your
expertise and all your you basically
packaging all your experience and your
expertise. And now you're selling that.
That's when you have, you know, ultra
high ticket coaching. That's when you
have uh consulting. That's where you
have software. That's where you have
ecom. And that's why I'm so against like
basically to me saying we we're using
ecom. People are going to hate me, but
we'll just use it for now. Uh when they
say ecom and beginners. Mhm. Like it
doesn't make any sense. It's like giving
an F1 car to a guy that want to get his
driving license. Like it wouldn't make
any sense. Well, there's a lot of
components, right? You need to
understand. There's so many components.
digital marketing,
um, building websites. There's not even
a place to start. There's just building
the product, logistics, shipping,
fulfillment. There's a lot of
components. The way I understood it was
like, you see, let's say you have a
marketing agency. Mhm. Most of your
clients would be ecom stores, for
example. Mhm. So, your entire business
is delivering a small portion of someone
else's business. You telling me? So like
you have whole agencies and business
models set up around helping a portion
of your business and you're telling me
that business is beginner friendly. I
see what you mean. Like how would that
make sense? Like you're saying even the
professionals would outsource. And it's
true because we have a marketing agency,
right? And one of our clients has a
massive ecom uh business. He does I
think $2 $300,000 a month
but he outsources marketing to us
because we're the experts in that
department. That's that's a very
powerful point. The thing is you're
saying that this setting up an
influencer marketing
agency. It just doesn't require that
type of insight and sophistication.
Anyone can do it. Yeah. So the way I go
about it, not anyone can do it. That's
why, by the way, not anyone can can make
it by the way. So that's why for for the
program we have a super strict uh
filtering process cuz alhamdulillah the
the success rate uh to to make sure we
can keep it that high. We need to make
sure who we let in cuz if you get me a
you know sorry if you're old and
watching this if you're 65 you never
been online I can give you the best
program on earth. You don't know what
influencer means. Like it would be lying
saying anyone you would be able to
succeed cuz it makes sense that you have
you only let certain type people in if
you've got 100% success rate so far.
Mhm. On the 100% success rate. There's a
guy that is getting me in trouble. Last
two weeks ago, that guy's about to break
the 100% success rate streak. Oh,
really? He had a little
issue. He was like 2 and a half months
into his his training and uh he was
putting in the efforts and somehow cuz
we we have a way to track I'll talk
about the 100% success rate part um and
how it's done. So, cuz a lot of people
make big claims. If you see the back
end, it starts to make it a lot more uh
believable. Basically 100% of the people
that apply was what start and and put in
the time into it which require four
hours a day of work every single day.
Uh-huh. Alhamdulillah 100% of those get
results. Which is closing deals, making
money, right? So the ones who do the
work, right? The ones who do what you
told them to do basically. Yeah. But
then there there's some people who put
like crazy
um they put like inactivable guarantees.
Mhm. So it's like yeah I refund you if
it doesn't work they have to send 1,000
emails a day for like 90 days straight
like you know no one's ever going to
send a thousand emails a day. Yeah.
They've set them up for failure. Yeah.
You say just do 3 4 hours of work. We
say no now it's installed is 4 hours a
day work
for how long? For the the program is 90
days. Okay. So 4 hours a day or for 90
days. Yeah. And you will make money
inshallah. Yeah. Alhamdulillah. If
you're doing that actually our students
make money within first or second month.
So it's like 45 days you're making money
and then you use the remaining 45 days
to so 90 days is just there as it's
there to catch the people who got a bit
slower you know cuz when you have the
average 45 days some guys are you know
30 days some guys are 60 days some are
70. But within 45 days people are making
money. Yeah. We've got a brother making
money in 5 days but that was how much
was he making? He closed a 9.5k deal.
9.5k euros, dollars, pounds, USD, he
made 2.5 profit. Allah 5 days into it.
That one I was in 5 days from signing up
to the Yeah, I didn't believe it when I
saw it. I messaged him. I can I can pull
it up. Yeah, we can put it on the
screen. Inshallah, what's what's the
what's what's the maximum amount any of
your students have made? I have some
that didn't disclose it or didn't want
to disclose it. Um I have a student that
made So, we're going to talk revenue and
then profit. Okay. We have a student
that closed
48,000 US worth of deals in his second
month. Oh wow. That that guy was tough.
We had him as a coach. Uh from there I
train him even more. And he was making
10 20% on that. He was he was actually
making more. He made about 13 to 15
profit on that. 15k USD. Yeah. In two
months. He's a but and for the guys
making excuses, he's a full-time
student. And he had he had a side job.
Um, so we basically was like, "All
right, scrap your side job. Let me hire
you as a coach. You're going to help me
train the brothers." Uh, cuz we had a
lot of events. I couldn't train everyone
else myself. So, I started getting
coaches in, training them, and they help
train more more brothers. We had another
guy closing a
42,000. So, it's actually more than the
first one. Wow. And on that one, I think
he was making 20 or 30%. Wow. A lot of
And same thing over second month. Um,
and then we got different guys. We got a
guy closing uh one one guy is closing a
longterm deal. So he's like closing a
yearly deal with a brand. I think it was
70 grand. Um but that's on a year. So
he's making like 30 grand but that's on
the year. So it's about 3k a month for
the entire year. Very good. And how long
how long until he got that deal? That
one got dragged along for so long. He
But it makes sense, right? It's a bigger
deal. It's 70k. He he basically closed
it around early like he he literally had
the agreement. It's like me and you say,
"Okay, we're going to do this. It's
fine." But the final handshake was done
like 2 months after the agreement
somehow cuz they got delayed and
everything sales cycle can be a bit
long. So, so fundamentally what you do
if I've understood correctly, right?
Because this sounds this sounds very
nice, right? And I'll be honest with
you, I get people coming to me all the
time saying, "Aki, I want to set up a
business." And I'm like, "Bro, I can't
help you. I don't take people 0ero to
one. I can't do that. I only work with
business owners." And even then, it's
it's it's people that are doing like
usually a lot of money, right? Like our
like even for example, this retreat that
we have, the qualification standard was
very high, right? 78 finger, right?
seven eight figure and then sometimes we
make exceptions for some very high six
figure entrepreneurs if you're like you
know what this guy really does have some
benefit to share or he'll probably will
receive or be there very soon we make
those exceptions right I think maybe we
have like two or three of those guys on
this time around but otherwise that's
our qualification standard but something
like this is needed to help these
brothers and can it help sisters no it
can't help sisters I mean the the we
because it's a mentorship we have you
know we talk to you one etc it's No, no,
no. It's be interesting. Maybe if you
can find a way to get a female mentor to
mentor the girls. Yeah. So far, my take
on I'm going to get harassed. My take on
on women in business is something else.
Not even me. I I I'm I'm not for women
like being career women and my
businesses, but I mean from that angle.
So, I rather not. I know that some
sisters who want who need to make money
and everything. It's becoming a lot more
common, man. For that one, I would not
do like a mentorship. You know what I
do? I rather just do like free content
and hourong uh trainings that they can
just take. Yeah. So it could be you see
how we said the 0 to2k for example
selling your time. It could be finding
great, you know, hal ways of making
money online where you don't have to
free mix, you have to interact with
people with with infant. There's a lot
of single mothers now, right? There's a
lot and I think it's needed, man. I used
to I'm be very against it and I still am
if there's no reason for a woman to do
it, but unfortunately it's a necessity
and it seems like a halal opportunity
where they could just be at home just
sending DMs and yeah, for for that one
sometimes you got to hop on calls. Not
always,
but so far I I've because the offer is
is still recent. We've just made it bare
simple. It's it's also an important
point. It's always looking for simple
stuff. See how I I going back to the
ecom thing. I was like, you want to
start with a small service based
business. You're making your money and
then you go to a bigger business. A note
on that one for ecom. I actually love
ecom, but that's when you want to make
millions. That's the worst. It's like
you're taking a a Lambo to drive 5 m an
hour. Like it wouldn't make any sense.
Mhm. That's why I'm I'm I'm going back
to it cuz some people would would say,
"Oh, why is he just pushing another
business to push his?" No, it's which
one does make sense for your current
situation. Which vehicle is is the right
one for where you are and where you want
to be. Mhm. So just like you see to get
there it was like 20 minutes. So I took
a a taxi. But to go from Algeria to
Dubai, I took a plane. M so I two
different vehicles to go from one place
to another depending on how it's not
that you hate planes or you hate taxis.
It's just that one is more appropriate
for a particular time and place.
Exactly. It's not I can't come in and
say yeah planes are the best vehicles
cuz imagine I was in my hotel room like
am I going to take a plane to come 5 km
I I can't do that. So just like you have
you know selling your time we can just
even bundle it in three categories. You
can say first you start by selling your
time then you sell your skills then you
sell your experience that's it. And to
me, selling your experience goes to
either you're doing some sort of
consulting or some sort of coaching,
some sort of courses, or
you bundling all your skills that you
had. So when you run multiple
businesses, you know about sales, you
know about marketing, you know about
delivery. Then you start a business that
requires all these skills, but that's
more rewarding. Mhm. Like ecom, it's
really hard to start it up, get it
rolling, but when you do it, it's
insanely scalable. Mhm. you know, you
don't need insane uh amount of people on
your team because it's product based.
So, you don't need everyone to go and
fulfill the delivery themselves, which
is the downside of service based
businesses. You you you struggle to get,
you know, a service based business above
eight figures. Mhm. Whereas ecom is is
really good for that because, you know,
you go start hiring, you know, 10 20
people and then your your problem
dayto-day is being a HR, is managing
people. Whereas with ecom, the guys when
they're starting out, they're
struggling. Mhm. But you get guys making
10 million a year and they have like a 5
10 people team and it's like yeah we're
just lean this guy does marketing this
guy does fulfillment and then we're good
and then they have a super lean business
which is the the the upside but you know
much much harder to start much more
capital much much bigger headache. No,
look, I'll be honest with you, right?
Being in this space for a while, what
you're saying makes a lot of sense to
me. Does seem like a very simple,
smooth, easy process for a beginner,
right? It some a vehicle that can take
someone from zero to one to get you to 5
to 10k a month. This can become a six
figure a year business. IMA, which is
influencer marketing, is to me, that's
why I made a video called the only halal
business worthy. The the only was not on
the halal. It was only the only worth.
Mhm. because I got some people coming at
me. I was like, it's only worth, it's
the only one I do believe is worth. Of
course, there's some marketing that goes
behind it. You can start another
business. And a point on that one, the
takeaway I want people to have from this
this podcast is not to start an IMA
honestly cuz alhamdulillah we already
have a lot of students. You have 240 50
plus just had like three new one today.
So, four new today. So it's
260 something.
Um
my goal hands down is that people have
that understanding of they should start
a service based business and then they
ask themselves which is the best service
based business to start and to me
in marketing was was one of them. Reason
being you're not tied to the service
delivery. Remember what I spoke about
when I said, you know, you start hiring
a lot of people and it starts to become
a a headache managing personal drag.
Yeah. Well, that's because you're doing
serious delivery yourself. So, like when
you have SMMA, for example, it is a
service based business. So, much better
to start when you're a beginner. Now,
the downside is you're doing all the
fulfillment yourself. You're running ads
for people. You're you're whatever lead
generation you're doing all the kind of
you're not doing any fulfillment. You're
just connecting the brand to the
influencer. You take commission. That is
correct. the brand to so the brand plays
the pays the influencer and you take a
cup from the deal that you connected you
broker the deal basically. Yeah. I'm
kind of a lazy guy when it comes to
business. Um or like I I like to
optimize everything. So I was like if
someone else can do delivery then you
don't have to. Yeah. And if even if I
charge a tenth of what I could make well
I can make 100 times the volume and I
would make 10 times more money.
So that's when I realized mil like the
whole thing be behind middleman
businesses and if you actually look at
the biggest companies right now on earth
like most of them are middleman
businesses you can look at any company
Uber doesn't have any cars
doesn't have any houses Amazon doesn't
have any products they do have they do
have products but fundamentally it's a
marketplace right no like most of them
sky scanner wow you're right subhan
allah just think about it you see when
you see when you spend money PayPal wow
Wow, you're right. You're spending money
with your with your card, Visa,
Mastercard. They're charging all your
like you're you're getting paid. You're
spending money. They're not involved.
They're taking their commissions.
They're taking their and that's which is
why for example like even in our
network, right? We have um a lot of
deals that happen like in the last just
uh couple of months. there's been $10
million in terms of
um transaction volume, terms of
investments that have taken place
between the brothers in the righteous
community. Alhamdulillah. So
if that deal takes place, let's just say
I connect someone to let's even take an
example there. There's an oil brand.
Yeah. And I know you I have your
WhatsApp number. I like your videos.
Let's not let's take a beginner. Let's
actually start an IMA live from scratch.
Okay. I'm a a random guy. I have no
money to my name whatsoever. I want to
make money. I want to start an
influencer marketing. What do I do?
That's decent free source. Mhm.
I I' I'd start
by okay, the the the important part is
to take the right steps in the right
order. Mhm. I like I said, I'm no name.
I have nothing to my name. M. So, I
can't really sell expensive stuff to
brands or close big deals on my name cuz
I have nothing to my name. Now, if I go
and I pull an influencer Mhm. and then
use his social proof and sell this Mhm.
they won't care about me. Yeah. Just
like if let's say you're Ronaldo's
manager. Yeah. You're saying, "Oh, look,
I've got access to Ronaldo." Of course,
it's influencers that are of a lot
lesser scale, but I've got access to so
and so. You get in touch with the
influencer and then you basically
leverage him when you go to the brand.
Exactly. They don't ask questions about
you cuz that's a main question we get is
like why would the brand pay me? Why
would they, you know, not work with the
influencer directly or like why who am I
to the influencer? Exactly. And a lot of
them don't have departments set up to
actually know which influencers are best
and ideal for them because they're
usually old people that are out of
touch. But this is one of the things
that you mentioned, right, is that
people who use social media, who
understand how the algorithms work
because they're day-to-day users of
these apps are probably going to be best
placed to make these deals cuz you're
already
basically a student of the trade by
using it every day. Yeah. No, I
definitely agree with you. The the the
the um the like I mentioned like when
when that transa like if someone makes a
1.5 million deal, you can you could just
take a 1% commission, right, just for
connecting people. Mhm. But then people
are like, "Whoa, it can't be that easy."
But it's actually not that easy. It took
a lot of effort to build that network,
right? It took a lot of efforts to build
that network and to first of all to most
of the efforts goes into things that
people have as prerequirements. Yeah.
And and by default knowledge and then
they say, "Oh, it's easy. It sounds too
easy." Well, no. You know about social
media cuz you spent 5 years crawling on
TikTok. So, you naturally learn it. To
you. It sounds like, "Oh, yeah. I know
about influencers. It couldn't be so
easy." Well, if you take a guy that
worked in a farm his whole life, he's
never going to be able to sell like the
same thing happened to me and it was it
was actually a big mind shift, right?
So, I built this brand for 10 years and
I didn't realize that I've got access to
people who need one another. So, there
was a brother who was selling properties
halal without connected him with a guy
and then he gave me commission and I
just give me 20k.
I didn't even believe it. Mhm. Like but
it's like I've naturally built this up
over a decade. But what you're saying
is people who don't even have an asset
like a brand that they built can just by
virtue of them using social media
because they know they they grew up in
this generation. They know how it works.
Go to an influencer, go to a brand, make
the deal and take 10 20%. Mhm. You can
even take more than that. Start getting
experience. So the the way it goes is
you start by by narrowing down who
you're going to work with. So you're
going to pick your niche. Mhm. So you go
with Muslim influencers or you go with
second foreigners or you pick whatever
the keepal of course. Of course that's
that's a Muslim podcast. Don't even have
to mention that. Do you avoid like
sometimes you important to mention?
Yeah. Then I can mention it. You avoid
things like fitness cuz people won't
cover the you avoid things like finance
cuz a lot of apps have all of that
stuff. But I get your point right. You
want to there there's obviously there is
the business activity is in within
itself halal but there are nuances
because you want to make sure you don't
work people that do haram. That's
correct. Simple. Okay. Look coming to
the halal element. So look this is very
interesting. Allah we spoke about it in
quite a lot of depth and I think anyone
who's watching now feels like maybe that
this could work for them. They can go to
the link below in I'll put the link
towards your uh your form. It's a you've
mentioned to me in the past very tough
qualification form. Yeah. Even
disclosingly before even anyone thinks
about applying, it's not a get-rich
quick scheme. You can't get rich just
like that. You have to work. When we say
4 hours, it's not 4 hours when you're
scrolling on your phone, you're doing
random stuff. You're sitting down in
front of your laptop for 4 hours. You're
not moving. It could be twice in the
morning, twice after. Um, you're not
moving. You're working on actual high
leverage task. Like you're not just
scrolling on on social media or trying
to do, you know, whatever. You're
actually sending emails. You're actually
doing cold call outreach. You're
actually finding new leads. You're
you're warming up the other leads.
You're doing proper work for four hours.
and this for weeks without seeing
results. If that's something you can do
and you're motivated to keep pushing,
then we can consider your application.
That's how you keep 100%. How many
applications do you decline on average?
So, we had I think we had over 10,000
people applying to the mentorship. And
you only 260 got in about that. Under 3%
got in. Wow. A lot better. And those are
uh 10-minute applications. So, like it's
not a quick one they just fill out, you
know, or you put you it's not like an
opt-in page. You just put your number
and your email. It's a a full type form,
six to you know some before during Cruz,
we had eight eight questions. Then you
have a first call initiation where we
learn a bit more about you. Then if you
make it to that step, you have another
call with um a closing call where you
get the the program present. Make sure
you obviously so you help these students
get results that they're actually going
to do the work. Mahab man, thank you man
so much for uh this podcast. We covered
so much and hopefully it's opened a lot
of brothers and you know their eyes to
uh the first step that they can take as
Muslim entrepreneurs you know from from
not being entrepreneurs to being
entrepreneurs and um you know I really
hope that people are going to search you
out inshallah come and check out your
Instagram your YouTube and if they feel
like they're ready to put in the 4 hours
a day right for um so if they you must I
can give some prerequis So that people
you take 10 minutes to apply to that.
Don't waste your time. If you need to
have four hours a day available, you
need to be we we actually enforcing this
one is is fairly new one. We we adding
in we we're taking people under 50, not
above and above 18. So 18 to 18 to 35 is
actually the sweet spot. Uh above that
we start to be even harder on you. So,
if you come on the call and you're like
45, we're going to actually try and push
you away and test you basically on the
spot about your knowledge about social
media, which is the third um requirement
we have is that you actually use social
media, you know about it, cuz you're
going to be working with influencers,
working with brands, if you never use
YouTube, never use Instagram, there's no
way we could have it even within the
time frame we have. So, and that could
also help people understand how we go
from like, oh, this sounds so easy, so
whatever to like, okay, makes more sense
because it sounds so easy because most
people have the pre- requirements that
it takes. They have the time they've
been, you know, their brain is fried
because they spend so much time on on
social media which is which fueled their
basically their knowledge base for that
business. It's it's just like imagine
you had you grew up in a your dad has a
coffee shop and you grew up in a you
know, seeing him every day. How easy
would that be for you to set up a coffee
shop? If you're successful within a year
of opening your coffee shop or three
months of opening a coffee shop, would
people say opening a coffee shop is easy
or would they say you had all the
requirements it took to open a coffee
shop then it was easy for you? That of
course. Yeah, that's why we have there.
So, man, look guys, if you feel like you
you've got those requirements, feel free
to apply. They had over 10,000
applications, less than 3% get in. And
who knows man if Allah decrees for you
and um you know you might get in in the
tip you know make toba for any sins that
you might have done before you apply
either way really I I hope people take
take away benefit from from this podcast
if we if we wrap it up because we
covered a lot of points if you want to
make money online start a service based
business look for ones that don't have a
lot of delivery attached to it because
it would help you scale
And then if you're trying to succeed
with a business, then you need to come
clean with Allah. That way, you know,
you're praying your fast, you're doing
everything properly. You make dua in
your giving charity to solve your
problems. Now, you got now you just got
to put in the work. And of course, we
mentioned
that. Pardon the interruption, but in
case you ever wanted to move to Dubai,
I've got something very special for you.
As you may be aware, myself and Abu Bakr
moved to Dubai and Sharah last year. It
was one of the best decisions that we
ever made for our dean, our families and
our businesses. Living here is amazing.
You got a message in almost every single
street. Unparalleled safety and
security. You got lessons from Mia and
different teachers and students of
knowledge in English and Arabic and no
income tax. Now, how do you move here?
That's a question that you might be
asking. Well, it can be tough if you
don't know your way around things.
Sometimes the companies that help you
get visas here, they got hidden fees,
long waits, big problems resulting in
visa rejections, a lot of wasted money
and time. This is where Ansad
Consultants comes into play. They helped
us set up everything. No hidden fees, no
long waits. They kept it simple and
honest. I got my visa in less than a
month. And these guys have a 100% track
record helping brothers get their visa
so far. 100% track record. That's
insane. Allah. Now, if you're thinking
of moving to the UAE, I recommend Ansard
Consultants. They can even help you
invest in properties hit with a 100%
Sharia compliant contract. So if you
want a smooth move like we did, click
the link below and check out
Consultants. Now back to the